

M ABDUL REHMAAN

Front End Developer

About Me

My objectives are to participate in practical projects, work with smart people, and have a better understanding of the full software development lifecycle. by utilizing my current expertise in front-end design and learning new ones



03407755917



rehmaankiani@gmail.com



Missa kaswal, Gujar khan Rawalpindi

SKILLS

- React.JS
- Html & css
- Adobe illestrator
- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Graphic Designing
- Design & Development

EXPERIENCE

Fiverr

2021 - 2023

i am still working on fiverr as a Graphic Designer and i have handled many projects with my clients from all over the world

Accenture call center 2019 - 2020

i worked as a part time employee in Accenture call center in Rehmanabad Rawalpindi.so i have some expertise in communication skill and in marketing skills.

EDUCATION

The University Of Lahore Isb campus

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering 2019-2023

Govt college Sarwar Shaheed G.K

FSc in Engineering 2016-2019

LANGUAGE

- English
- Urdu